const questions = [
  {
    question: "Who won the 2024 24 hours of Le Mans in Hyper Car category?",
    options: ["Alpine", "Ferrari", "Toyota", "Porsche"],
    answer: "Ferrari",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is current reining World Champion in F1?",
    options: [
      "Fernando Alonso",
      "Lewis Hamilton",
      "Max Verstappen",
      "Charles Leclerc",
    ],
    answer: "Max Verstappen",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a Triple Crown Race?",
    options: ["Monaco GP", "24h of Le Mans", "Monza GP", "Indianopolis 500"],
    answer: "Monza GP",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the 2024 Monaco GP?",
    options: ["Alpine", "Ferrari", "McLaren", "RedBull"],
    answer: "Ferrari",
  },
  {
    question: "Where F1 tests new cars aka Pre Season Testing?",
    options: ["Silverstone", "Australia", "Barcelona", "Bahrain"],
    answer: "Bahrain",
  },
  {
    question: "Which driver has no. 16 on current F1 grid?",
    options: [
        "Fernando Alonso",
        "Lewis Hamilton",
        "Max Verstappen",
        "Charles Leclerc",
      ],
      answer: "Charles Leclerc",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of following driver is not multiple grand prix winner?",
    options: [
        "Carlos Sainz",
        "Lando Norris",
        "Max Verstappen",
        "Charles Leclerc",
      ],
      answer: "Lando Norris",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Team is currently leading Constructors Championship in F1?",
    options: ["Mercedes", "Ferrari", "McLaren", "Red Bull"],
    answer: "Red Bull",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Team is currently leading Manufacturing Championship in WEC?",
    options: ["Alpine", "Ferrari", "Toyota", "Porsche"],
    answer: "Porsche",
  },
  {
    question: "Full Form of F1?",
    options: ["Fast1", "Ferrari1", "Formula1", "Forever1"],
    answer: "Formula1",
  },
];

export default questions;
